export default data = [
  {
      question: "The sign in front of the Johnsonsâ€™ house says that no one is allowed to set foot on their ______ without permission.",
      options: ["margin","shelter","reservation","property"],
      correct_option: "property"
  },
  {
      question: "Instead of giving negative criticism, our teachers usually try to give us ______ feedback so that we can improve on our papers.",
      options: ["absolute","constructive","influential","peculiar"],
      correct_option: "constructive"
  },
  {
      question: "A study shows that the chance of an accident is much higher for drivers who are ______ in phone conversations while driving.",
      options: ["contained","engaged","included","located"],
      correct_option: "engaged"
  },
  {
      question: "Mike trembled with ______ and admiration when he saw the magnificent view of the waterfalls.",
      options: ["awe","plea","oath","merit"],
      correct_option: "awe"
  },
  {
      question: "Ms. Chen has a large collection of books and most of them are quite heavy; she needs a bookshelf ______ enough to hold all of them.",
      options: ["coarse","vigorous","portable","sturdy"],
      correct_option: "sturdy"
  },
  {
      question: "The athlete rolled up his sleeves to show his ______ forearms, thick and strong from years of training in weight-lifting. ",
      options: ["barren","chubby","ragged","muscular"],
      correct_option: "muscular"
  },
  {
      question: "Suffering from a serious financial crisis, the car company is now on the edge of ______, especially with the recent sharp decrease in its new car sales.",
      options: ["graduation","capacity","depression","bankruptcy"],
      correct_option: "bankruptcy"
  },
  {
      question: "After the rain, the meadow ______ under the sun with the droplets of water on the grass.",
      options: ["rippled","shattered","glistened","mingled"],
      correct_option: "glistened"
  },
  {
      question: "The Great Wall of China was originally built to ______ the northern border of the country against foreign invasion.",
      options: ["fortify","rehearse","diminish","strangle"],
      correct_option: "fortify"
  },
  {
      question: "A mad scientist in a novel is often portrayed as a wild-eyed man with crazy hair, working ______ in a lab full of strange equipment and bubbling test tubes.",
      options: ["contagiously","distinctively","frantically","tremendously"],
      correct_option: "frantically"
  },
]